shopping-feed.com 2019-07-26

# 

SHOPPING FEED PRIVACY POLICY
Shopping Feed (the “Company”) is committed to maintaining robust privacy protections for
its users. Our Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to help you understand how we
collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making
informed decisions when using our Service.
For purposes of this Agreement, “Site” refers to the Company’s website, which can be
accessed at www.shopping-feed.com.
“Service” refers to the Company’s services accessed a software-as-a-service, or SaaS, in
which users can integrate, manage and optimize their merchandise sales across hundreds
of online channels accessed through a standard web browser, which provides clients with a
single, integrated user interface to manage product listings, inventory availability, pricing
optimization, search terms, data analytics and other critical functions across these channels
via the Company’s software available on shopping-fee.com
The terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to the Company.
“You” refers to you, as a user of our Site or our Service.
By accessing our Site or our Service, you accept our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use
(found here: https://www.shopping-feed.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/Shopping-Feed-
Terms-of-Use.pdf), and you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your
Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.
I.          INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We collect “Non-Personal Information” and “Personal Information.” Non-Personal Information
includes information that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as anonymous usage
data, general demographic information we may collect, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform
types, preferences you submit and preferences that are generated based on the data you
   Phone: (920) 333 3488 Email: contact@shopping-feed.com       Website: www.shopping-feed.com
                                                1

submit and number of clicks. Personal Information includes your email (most of the time, a
professional one) you provided us to open your account, and address for invoicing. which you
submit to us through the registration process at the software.
     1. Information collected via Technology
To activate the Service you do not need to submit any Personal or Professional Information
other than your email address. To use the Service thereafter, you do need to submit further
Personal Information which may include First and Last name, address and number of
employees in your company. However, in an effort to improve the quality of the Service, we
track information provided to us by your browser or by our software application when you
view or use the Service, such as the page you visit on our website and on our software
(known as the “referring URL”), the type of browser you use, the device from which you
connected to the Service, the time and date of access, and other information that does not
personally identify you. We track this information using cookies, or small text files which
include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to a user’s browser from our
servers and are stored on the user’s computer hard drive. Sending a cookie to a user’s
browser enables us to collect Non-Personal information about that user and keep a record
of the user’s preferences when utilizing our services, both on an individual and aggregate
basis. For example, the Company may use cookies to collect the following information:
· your login, date of your last connection (for the use of our TimeLine feature), which
emails you opened or not (via software like AutopilotHQ and Intercom) etc.
We may share Personal et Professional Information (like a range of your revenue on
channels, your number of products, your Ecommerce CMS technology) with our partners in
the case we would like to recommend you to them. In general, this is on the aim to grow
your business.
   Phone: (920) 333 3488 Email: contact@shopping-feed.com      Website: www.shopping-feed.com
                                                 2

The Company may use both persistent and session cookies; persistent cookies remain on
your computer after you close your session and until you delete them, while session cookies
expire when you close your browser.
      2. Information you provide us by registering for an account
In addition to the information provided automatically by your browser when you visit the
Site, to become a subscriber to the Service you will need to create a profesional profile. You
can create a profile by registering with the Service and entering your email address, and
creating a user name and a password. By registering, you are authorizing us to collect,
store and use your email address in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
         3. Children’s Privacy
The Service is not directed to anyone under the age of 13. The Software does not
knowingly collect or solicit information from anyone under the age of 13, or allow anyone
under the age of 13 to sign up for the Service. In the event that we learn that we have
gathered personal information from anyone under the age of 13 without the consent of a
parent or guardian, we will delete that information as soon as possible. If you believe we
have collected such information, please contact us at contact@shopping-feed.com.
II.         HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION
Personal Information:
Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise
share for marketing purposes your Personal Information with third parties without your
consent. We do share Personal Information with vendors who are performing services for
    Phone: (920) 333 3488 Email: contact@shopping-feed.com    Website: www.shopping-feed.com
                                                3

the Company, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access
to user’s email address for purposes of sending emails from us. Those vendors use your
Personal Information only at our direction and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.
In general, the Personal Information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with
you. For example, we use Personal Information to contact users in response to questions,
solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional
offers.
We may share Personal et Professional Information (like a range of your revenue on
channels, your number of products, your Ecommerce CMS technology) with outside parties
if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information
is reasonably necessary to meet any applicable legal process or enforceable governmental
request; to enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential
violations; address fraud, security or technical concerns; or to protect against harm to the
rights, property, or safety of our users or the public as required or permitted by law.
Non-Personal Information
In general, we use Non-Personal Information to help us improve the Service and customize
the user experience. We also aggregate Non-Personal Information in order to track trends
and analyze use patterns on the Site. This Privacy Policy does not limit in any way our use
or disclosure of Non-Personal Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such
Non-Personal Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our
discretion.
In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another
company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your Personal Information may be among
the assets transferred. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and
   Phone: (920) 333  3488 Email: contact@shopping-feed.com      Website: www.shopping-feed.com
                                                 4

are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to
process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If our information
practices change at any time in the future, we will post the policy changes to the Site so that
you may opt out of the new information practices. We suggest that you check the Site
periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.
III.       HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION
We implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized
access. Your account is protected by your account password and we urge you to take steps
to keep your personal information safe by not disclosing your password and by logging out
of your account after each use. We further protect your information from potential security
breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption,
firewalls and secure socket layer technology. However, these measures do not guarantee
that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such
firewalls and secure server software. By using our Service, you acknowledge that you
understand and agree to assume these risks.
IV.        YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes.
 When we send a promotional communication to a user, the user can opt out of further
promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each
promotional e-mail. You can also indicate that you do not wish to receive marketing
communications from us in the software. Please note that notwithstanding the promotional
preferences you indicate by either unsubscribing or opting out in the software, we may
   Phone: (920) 333  3488 Email: contact@shopping-feed.com    Website: www.shopping-feed.com
                                               5

continue to send you administrative emails including, for example, periodic updates to our
Privacy Policy, technical changes or invoices.
V.          LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
As part of the Service, we may provide links to or compatibility with other websites or
applications. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those
websites or the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to
information collected by us through the Site and the Service. Therefore, this Privacy Policy
does not apply to your use of a third party website accessed by selecting a link on our Site
or via our Service. To the extent that you access or use the Service through or on another
website or application, then the privacy policy of that other website or application will apply
to your access or use of that site or application. We encourage our users to read the privacy
statements of other websites before proceeding to use them.
VI.        CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
The Company reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time.
 We will notify you of significant changes to our Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the
primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our
site. Significant changes will go into effect 30 days following such notification. Non-material
changes or clarifications will take effect immediately. You should periodically check the Site
and this privacy page for updates.
VII.      CONTACT US
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please
contact us by sending an email to contact@shopping-feed.com
Last Updated: This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 29th 2018.
   Phone: (920) 333 3488 Email: contact@shopping-feed.com       Website: www.shopping-feed.com
                                                 6
